(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-08T23:33:44.255579",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon.
公演中のフラッシュライトにご注意ください。
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し、応援していただいてOKです。
Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon.
公演中のフラッシュライトにご注意ください。
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し、応援していただいてOKです。
Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演までしばしお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment.
Attention For Visitors
演出上、激しい光の点滅がございます。
声出しでの応援は問題ございません。
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演までしばしお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment.
Attention For Visitors
演出上、激しい光の点滅がございます。
声出しでの応援は問題ございません。
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment.
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is OK.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment.
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is OK.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までもうしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a little longer.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までもうしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a little longer.
Attention For Visitors
[Notice] Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
[Merchandise] 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment.
Attention For Visitors
[Notice] Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
[Merchandise] 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
キアラ！キアラ！
Kiara! Kiara!
イナ！イナ！
Ina! Ina!
おー！
Oh!
Thank you all so much for coming to...
...Takanashi Kiara and Ninomae Ina'nis's first concert, DRAW TO DAWN!
Kikkeriki!
I am Takanashi Kiara, and...
Good morning, afternoon, evening everyone! It's Ninomae Ina'nis!
That's right, it's finally time for our concert!
Is everyone hyped?!
Before we kick things off, we have some important safety rules and house guidelines to go over.
First, photography and the use of any recording equipment are strictly prohibited during the performance.
Also, the venue is smoke-free, so please refrain from smoking inside.
But what... but what if I'm smoking hot?
Oh, Ina!
If you start feeling unwell at any point, please don't push yourself.
Just reach out to the nearest staff member for help. And hydrate!
For everyone's safety, please avoid any dangerous or disruptive behavior. This includes mashing...
No mashing? I mean it!
...moshing, diving, sitting on shoulders...
...jumping excessively, or throwing objects towards the stage.
Climbing onto the stage, intentionally blocking the aisles, or rushing toward the front is also (surprise!) not allowed.
Please refrain from disruptive shouting, erratic lightstick movements...
...or any extreme motions that might interfere with the experience of those around you. Be considerate.
If you don't follow the instructions of our staff or the venue staff, you may be asked to leave the venue.
Yes, please keep in mind that the venue organizers, performers, and staff...
...cannot be held responsible for any accidents, equipment damage, or trouble caused by failing to follow instructions.
Additionally, any costs for damages resulting from ignoring these rules...
...will be the responsibility of the person involved. So, be careful, guys, okay?
Oh, there are cameras in the venue for filming and photography today...
...and you might appear in footage or photos. These may be used for promotional purposes later on...,s:
...and you might appear in footage or photos. These may be used for promotional purposes later on...
...so please keep that in mind. Y'all are looking cute!
And finally, big news! Today's concert will be in two parts!
There's a part for Kiara and a part for me, so please look forward to both of them!
All right, that is it for the rules!
The show is about to begin, so get ready!
Bye-bye! See ya!
Takotori! Takotori! Takotori! Takotori!
タコダチ！タコダチ！
Takodachi! Takodachi!
イナ！イナ！イナ！イナ！
Ina! Ina! Ina! Ina!
Wah! Wah! Wah! Wah!
タコダチ！タコダチ！
Takodachi! Takodachi!
イナ！イナ！イナ！イナ！
Ina! Ina! Ina! Ina!
タコダチ！タコダチ！イナ！イナ！
Takodachi! Takodachi! Ina! Ina!
Enlightened by the powers that be
The ruler of a world run on inasanity
It's clear to me they still can't see
I'm just a normal girl
Empowered by the ancient one's call
We're gonna be punstoppable, we're not a cult
Nonsensical and nautical adventures lie in wait!
Gimme a one eight!
ichi! hachi! takodachi!
One! Eight! Takodachi!
ina ina ina
ina ina
俺のイナの世界線
To protect my Ina timeline...
守るためにタコになろう！！
I'll become a tako!
ichi! hachi! takodachi!
One! Eight! Takodachi!
ina ina ina
ina ina
いいタコになりますように
Hoping to become a good tako...
in a sanity で踊りましょう！
Let's dance in a sanity!
think of all that you could be ...
Think of all that you could be...
we're talking evolution, leave it all to me !
We're talking evolution, leave it all to me!
maybe just a touch of purple ink ...
Maybe just a touch of purple ink...
what'cha think ?
What'cha think?
it's a song you can't ignore
the ancient ones are calling you to be so much more !
The ancient ones are calling you to be so much more!
just put your hand in mine and be reborn ...
Just put your hand in mine and be reborn...
ina blink !
In a blink!
tell me what those legs are for ?
Tell me what those legs are for?
俺のイナ運ぶためです！
They're for carrying my Ina!
you could use 6 more !
You could use six more!
感謝感謝！ありがたい！！！
So grateful! Thank you so much!!!
we could all get matching ears !
We could all get matching ears!
they aren't really ears though ...
They aren't really ears though...
eh-??
sleepy eyes to fight your fears !
Sleepy eyes to fight your fears!
例えばイナいないの世界！！！
For example, a world without Ina!!!
alright, listen to my song, am i striking a chord with you ?
Alright, listen to my song, am I striking a chord with you?
stringing you along, so don't let me get bored of you !
Stringing you along, so don't let me get bored of you!
80 million strong and we've still got some more to do
Eighty million strong and we've still got some more to do
everybody shout ! world domination !!!
Everybody shout! World domination!!!
can i bank on your emotion ?
Can I bank on your emotion?
do i have you invested ?
Do I have you invested?
i don't wanna hear you say that you're not in ate rested !
I don't wanna hear you say that you're not in-ate-rested!
your unwavering devotion isn't all i've requested
do you care ? are you aware that you're my dearest creations ?!
Do you care? Are you aware that you're my dearest creations?!
oya oya ! a cute little takodachi found its way here ...
Oh my! A cute little takodachi found its way here...
いいタコだちの作り方！
How to make a good takodachi!
ひっくりかえして丸くして
Flip it over, make it round
コロコロまわして焦がさずに
Roll it around, don't let it burn
外はカリッと中ふわふわ
Crispy on the outside, fluffy on the inside
できたらソースでさあいただき！
Once done, add some sauce, and let's eat!
by the powers that be
the ruler of a world run on inasanity
it's clear to me they still can't see
i'm just a normal girl !
I'm just a normal girl!
empowered by the ancient one's call
we're gonna be punstoppable, we're not a cult
nonsensical and nautical adventures lie in wait
let's tako bout the future to be
rewriting all of history in urgency
with cookies as our currency ,
With cookies as our currency,
this place can finally heal !
This place can finally heal!
in a - subordination won't fly
In a-subordination won't fly
or else i'm making takoyaki tabehoudie
Or else I'm making all-you-can-eat takoyaki
no doubt about it
scream and shout it
welcome to my wah rld !!
Welcome to my WAHrld!!
so , it all goes back to eight and one
So, it all goes back to eight and one
it's only world domination, and we've just begun
ah , what a place of never ending fun !
Ah, what a place of never ending fun!
i want the world dyed in violet before i'm done !
I want the world dyed in violet before I'm done!
ina ina in a !
Ina ina in a!
ina in a !
Ina in a!
ina ina in a !
Ina ina in a!
ina in a !
Ina in a!
ina ina in a !
Ina ina in a!
ina in a !
Ina in a!
Drawn to Dawn
[Title: Drawn to Dawn]
キッキリキー！
Kikki-riki!
Welcome to Day 1 of Drawn to Dawn!
I am Takanashi Kiara!
キッキリキーだ！
Kikki-riki!
瞬く星の揺りかご
Beneath the cradle of twinkling stars,
欠けた台詞を繋ぎ合わせた memory
I pieced together the missing fragments of my memories.
聖なる従者が伝う
The sacred followers pass down
神話の理
the laws of myth.
祈りに耳を澄ませ
Listen closely to the prayers.
tell me, I can hear it clearly, tell me
声なき声に
...to the voiceless voice.
荒ぶる鼓動は弱さを焦がす
My wild heartbeat burns away my weakness.
炎 降り注ぐ空に身をやつして
Disguising myself in the sky where fire rains down,
乱れ咲くアカは紅化粧
the wildly blooming red is my crimson makeup.
数多重なる試練も生き抜いてみせる
I will survive through countless overlapping trials.
I will live to keep on fighting till the dawn
はい！はい！はい！はい！Louder!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Louder!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Go! Go! Go! Go!
たとえば先の見えない
Even if I wander into the boundary...
零の境界
...of absolute zero where the future is unseen,
迷い込んだとしても
even if I am lost...
何度も繰り返される
...and face a lonely end
孤高の終焉
repeated over and over,
そこに残った answer
I will reach the answer left behind.
don't break, I will never give up, don't break
羽が朽ちても
even if my feathers decay.
消せない強さは時の導
This unerasable strength is the guide of time.
灰花 舞い上がる大地
Slipping through the earth
身をくぐらせ
where ash flowers dance up,
燃ゆる朱の中 目を覚ます
I awaken amidst the burning vermillion.
刃交わる切っ先
With our crossing blades,
交わした契りは
the vow we made...
lies and truth, come to light at the break of day
...lies and truth, will come to light at the break of day.
I've been trying to find my destiny
but they keep pushing and pulling me astray
if I go wrong, what awaits me in the dark
could you tell me please, where I need to go?
tell me, I can hear it clearly, tell me
声なき声に
...to the voiceless voice.
漲る決意は暗闇を晴らす
My overflowing resolve clears away the darkness.
炎 降り注ぐ空に身をやつして
Disguising myself in the sky where fire rains down,
乱れ咲くアカは紅化粧
the wildly blooming red is my crimson makeup.
数多重なる試練も生き抜いてみせる
I will survive through countless overlapping trials.
blazing flames, show me the path to luminance
and in the next life too I promise, I will find you
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Clap your hands!
Lying down on the floor, late night...
...and you don't know, don't know, don't know what to do.
Hard to tell what's wrong, what's right...
...if yes or no, don't know, don't know, don't know what to do.
The storm hits hard and you're losing the way.
Just take a chance and dance in the rain.
'Cause you got the key, never throw it away.
Don't forget, don't forget what I said.
Get out of your head!
Life is only what you make it, you're gonna be okay.
So go ahead and do it, do it!
If you want it, let's get to it.
Everybody's gonna know your name!
'Cause sparks light the flame,
turn the dark of the night into day.
Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way.
So don't be afraid,
trust your heart, keep your head in the game.
Keep up, keep up, and never be afraid.
Gotta make it hot like a volcano,
strike a match and burn it up.
Kick your feet against the table,
to the beat of your own drum.
Sparks light the flame, so don't wait,
start a fire today.
Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way.
We ain't looking back, take the fast lane now,
in the driver's seat strapped, they just gasp out loud.
Going so fast that it shouldn't be allowed,
that's how we like it, you heard what I said.
Get out of your head!
Life is only what you make it, you're gonna be okay.
So take a step and move it, move it.
'Less you try, you won't get through it.
Everybody's gonna know your name!
'Cause sparks light the flame,
turn the dark of the night into day.
Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way.
So don't be afraid,
trust your heart, keep your head in the game.
Keep up, keep up, and never be afraid.
Let go of the past tonight,
choose the future only you define.
Even when the flames burn too bright, you're alive.
From the ashes, you rise!
Clap! Clap! Clap!
Everybody!
'Cause sparks light the flame,
turn the dark of the night into day.
Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way.
So don't be afraid,
trust your heart, keep your head in the game.
Keep up, keep up, and never be afraid.
Gotta make it hot like a volcano,
strike a match and burn it up.
Kick your feet against the table,
to the beat of your own drum.
Sparks light the flame, so don't wait,
start a fire today.
Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way.
Oh yeah!
Whoa!
Ki-Ki-Ri-Ki!
Ah!
Hello! Welcome, everybody, to...
...Takanashi Kiara and Hololive English's first ever concert...
...Connect the World!
Whoa!
I can hear you guys so clearly!
And I can see you guys so clearly, yeah!
Hi hi, everyone! Hello, hello!
Oh my god!
We're in Los Angeles!
Yay!
So, we started off with the iconic and classic songs of mine...
...HINOTORI and Sparks!
Don't we love those songs? Was that hype?
Yeah!
Yeah, you guys know like, HINOTORI was my first ever original song to put out...
...and yeah, it was like the beginning of my music...
...history, my musical journey,
and it's a song that means a lot to me,
and it's just so hype. It was also the first ever
time that I appeared in 3D, I think, long time ago
at Fes in Japan, right? Remember?
Good times! Yeah!
Thanks so much for cheering so loudly! You did so well!
Yeah!
I have been training so hard the past months in the gym,
trying to get stamina for this day,
because I think I learned about...
I learned and relearned about twenty choreographies!
What?! Crazy, right? Damn,
that was a lot of work. But...
finally, the day has come to show it all to all of you!
I want to say hi, by the way,
to all the live viewers worldwide!
There's so many cinemas showing this concert right now!
Hello, world!
Can you hear me? I wonder if I can hear them.
Can I hear them over the continents?
Well, that's you guys!
But I think I can hear them, yeah!
Also, there is some colleagues watching on YouTube right now,
like Ollie and all the EN members!
Hi! Thank you!
So excited!
I... I have to give a little bit of an announcement from my side, actually,
because it's very important. It has to be in the free part, because everybody needs to hear this.
My new album, Vogelfrei... you bought it, right?
Thank you!
But in case you didn't,
a second round of album sales has begun!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. So if you missed it previously or you want a new copy,
starting from Saturday, March 28th, at 11 PM,
I don't know which timezone!
Who knows? We'll find out, probably JST.
You will be able to order Vogelfrei again! So please everybody, order Vogelfrei!
So far, the songs that I performed up until now were not even from Vogelfrei, but don't worry...
I'm squeezing everything in that I can!
Yeah!
Okay, guys, you're probably aware of this,
but the free part usually ends...
after an MC.
But the free part only had two songs!
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't worry, I told staff, "We can't be having that, I want the free part to have a little bit more!"
Yeah!
So it will continue a little bit more, and then it will cut before another MC, so just so you know.
And then, once it cuts,
please, streaming tickets are available still in the description and in the pinned comments!
Probably there!
Yeah, so make sure to get your ticket because what you haven't even seen yet
is my colleague, Ninomae Ina'nis, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. The concert is split in half, so today you only have me in the free part,
but later if you want to see more of Wawa and Ina, go get streaming tickets! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Okay.
So with that, it is time to move on to many other songs! All right.
Are you ready?
All right! Here is the next song. Enjoy!
Passing by the familiar roads
I couldn't find the reason why
Who I am, you couldn't know
Stuck in the ruins
My dissolution
In between a dual reality
My only desire keeps me near you
Moving faster than the light can
I'm in the abstract, I...
...alone looking back
Did I lose my way?
I can't see the day
When I can reach you again
Then can I let go?
I can hear your voice
Leading me through the void
Fade away
To the grey
Eternally
I'm walking by
The lives that flash before my eyes
Alone, the silence deafening
Still I'm reaching out to you
Connections sacrificed
The lie
I tell myself so I'll survive
One day, eventually the light
It will lead me back
Do you see me?
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da ooh
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da, I am the wanderer
I'm tired of the same song
Every day like it's on repeat
I need a risky breakdown
Oh, honey
The night is falling
We don't need a steady symphony
Can you make it a little richer now?
Take me away
Like it's just the two of us
I'm ready
Do you feel the music, baby?
Meet me underneath the strobe light
Come alive
Move my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat, keep me dancing
Fever Night, thrill me
ココロコトバ合わせてよ follow my heartbeat
Align your heart and words, follow my heartbeat
バタバタバラバラバラバリンパ
Batabata barabara barabarinpa
聴かせてあげる
I'll let you hear it
ココロのバタフライ合わせて follow my heartbeat
Align your heart's butterfly, follow my heartbeat
イチ、ニ、サン、シ、rhythm!
1, 2, 3, 4, rhythm!
I'm in a trance of the way that you're moving
You got me shining, glowing like a prism
That disco ball makes me wild
Don't care who's watching us, so baby...
Meet me underneath the strobe light
Come alive
Moving my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat, keep me dancing
Fever Night, thrill me
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat, keep me dancing
Fever Night, thrill me
Baby
Keep me dancing till the daylight
Like crazy
Stop this sound from making a feud
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴、ご声援ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!